I wanted to ask you about lodos and
because this is something that it's kind
of come in and out of the TRT community
over the last few years. It was popular,
it wasn't popular, and now it is. And as
someone who's got multiple disc
herniations, it was something that when
I first heard about it, I was like,
"Okay, this is interesting." And then
when I looked into it, I was like,
"Well, this is a like a a progesterine
analog, which I don't really like the
sound of." But when I was looking at the
proposed mechanisms of the opioid
receptor, I was like this this I I I
don't really know if there's anything
here. And when I watched your take on
why nandelone is garbage, this to me
just made a huge amount of sense. So do
you think there is any merit or
application for augmenting a TRT
protocol with Dandelone for people who
love drug? No, it's just bro science
[__] that's being used by the bros
scientist salesman for a TRT company to
trick ignorant patients into believing,
oh, you've got pain, we'll take your
pain away. That it basically it's no
different than the Sackler family,
except for the at least their drug
worked. that the whole premise is this,
that
one, you're holding a [__] ton of water,
so your joints are going to be more
lubricated because every [__] in
America is dehydrated because no one
drinks enough water and no one uses
enough salt to stay hydrated. One. Two,
that it does upregulate collagen
synthesis.
2 A, so does every [__] thing else.
Okay, that's it. And then 2B, it doesn't
even increase collagen synthesis as much
as EQ. But EQ does decrease estrogen,
which would make you dehydrated, unless
you watch the hydration video I have.
And that pretty much it's how to grow
episode 11 hydration, which is one of
the most important videos I've ever
shot. It's one of the least popular
videos because it's something that
everyone can do for free to make their
life a million times better. They're not
going to do that. Not when they could
spend $200 a month on a bottle of
testosterone that they could have bought
of higher quality for 40. Why would you
do that? The fact that it costs more
means it must be better, right? No.
Drugs are like women's fashion. The
amount it costs has nothing to do with
the quality. It's just marketing. That
men think that drugs are like tools and
that you get what you pay for. Drugs are
not like tools. You do not get what you
pay for. That you want to buy the the
cheapest drugs you can because they're
it's all markup. Everything's a,000%
markup.
Like um supplements for instance, like
the supplement you pay $50 a month, the
pre-workout you pay $50 a month for that
cost like six bucks to make. You know,
you're paying all markup. You're paying
for their marketing and you're paying
for all the broken containers and the
amount of their inventory that's going
to go bad that they're predicting
they're going to lose profit on. Like I
pay $24 per container for my pre-workout
and I charge the same price as everyone
else does cuz I don't give a [__] if I
have any money. I just want to put
everyone else out of business. That's
the whole point is eventually after 10
years when I wipe out all other brands
on earth then I will actually start
making a profit because I'll have such a
huge market shares my shitty margins
will be fine. And that's the same
approach everyone should have towards
business is. But that's not how health
care is. People expect to get [__]
over by their healthcare provider. They
expect to get lied to. They expect to
get overcharged and they expect to get
shitty service. Where with an
underground lab, they give you they
overd deliver on concentration. They
give you next day shipping. They usually
do free shipping. Sometimes they throw
in extra bottles because they like you.
and they just are excellent business
people and do an excellent product, but
the HRT and the medical community lie to
you and give you propaganda that
underground labs are [__] and you have
to go with pharma because it's almost
like the Democrats are telling people
Republicans are evil. You should vote
Democrat. And the Republicans are like,
"Hey, but if you vote for us, you get
you don't have to pay as much taxes."
And people still vote Democrat. And it's
like it doesn't make any sense. It's
like, "Wait a minute, wait a minute wait
a minute.
Why the [__] would you vote for people
that are going to cost you more money?
Just vote for the people that are going
to improve your quality of life. Let the
special interest people vote for
themsel. You vote for yourself. If
everyone voted for themsel, everything
would be fine. It's the same thing with
the TRT and the underground community.
The underground labs are not out there
telling you don't buy TRT, don't buy
pharma, buy our underground stuff
instead. No, they're like, "We're doing
business correctly, and we've got such
good repeat business. Go ahead, try the
competition. Go try a TRT clinic. Wait
three weeks to get your bottle of
testosterone. Have it be underdosed.
Have them send you 19 gauge needles.
Then, instead of the 21 instead of the
23 or 25 or 27 gauge needles you should
be using, then when you run out, you
call to get a refill, wait 3 weeks to
get more drugs. See how you feel after 2
weeks of having no testosterone. Then
you get another bottle that lasts, they
only give you a half of a bottle that
lasts four weeks. Then you spend another
$200 and then you have to wait another
three weeks to get another bottle that's
only going to last you a month. Or you
could just go to an underground lab and
be like, I want to buy 10 bottles of
test. I want to have enough test to last
me for two years because there's a
shortage in China. And people are like,
okay, here you go. Boop. And you pay
like 300 bucks and you get through 10
bottles of testosterone. It's going to
last you three years. You know, like why
on earth would you spend 300 for 10
bottles when you could spend 200 for one
bottle? Because you're [__] stupid if
you because people are so [__]
stupid. They'd rather buy a bottle for
200 than 10 bottles for 300 because they
think it's better. And it's not.
Especially when the underground labs
have [__] tests from Janoshik or
Eliza showing that in Poland or in
wherever Janoshik is, it's like here we
go. We got the exact purity. We have the
exact molecular weight. We have the
exact chemical structure. But the dumb
asses who go to the TRT clinics can't
read a goddamn lab report on the product
to see that it's actually better than
the TRT clinics. Do the TRT clinics have
any lab reports showing the quality of
their compoundies? No. A compound
pharmacy is just a shitty underground
lab that spent all their money bribing
the FDA to get FDA approval. that the
underground labs are a million times
better than the compoundies.
So your question was what I got on a
tangent about how much I hate
compoundies and TRT
>> that uh nandelone doesn't really have a
place in the
>> T. Okay, so the what they do is they try
to sell you on Nanderlone that it's
going to improve collagen synthesis and
make pain go away, but EQ is better for
collagen synthesis. Anavar is about as
good for collagen synthesis.
Testosterone is great for collagen
synthesis. Testosterone also causes an
increase in water retention. So
nandrallone doesn't do anything
testosterone doesn't do except nandelone
doesn't convert to DHT and testosterone
does. And nandelone also is going to
upregulate the receptor, the estrogen
alpha receptor, so that any amount of
estrogen in your body is going to almost
guarantee give you gyno. So it's a [__]
drug. If someone really has that much
pain,
they got to a learn how to lift right.
Quit with the [__] flat barbell
benching. Grow the [__] up and use
proper bodybuilding exercises, not that
powerlifting [__] Don't be doing
sets less than 12 reps. Don't listen to
Paul Carter with this four to six rep
[__] Keep your reps in a double-
digit rep range if especially if you're
over 40, especially if you're on
anabolics because the anabolics grow
muscle faster than tendons. The reason
your tendons hurt is because you're
lifting too [__] heavy with dumb ass
exercises. Don't use barbells. They're
fixed bar movements. There's no way your
body is going to move. This is what your
chest does. Notice where my hands are.
This is not the smart movement. This is
so dumbbells or a converging arm
machine. Notice the path of the of the
humorous is at a 45 degree angle with a
slight internal rotation at the top.
That's what the pec does. You don't get
any of that with a barbell. Barbells are
[__] [__] That barbells are as
useless as five reps or less, which is
as useless as TRT clinics. You always
want to go with the best underground lab
that has real results. And then you can
pick the drug you want. You don't have
to use whatever they want to give you.
The garbage basement drugs like
Nandelone or Anadrol you or Winstrol.
You can use really good drugs like
Masteron or DHB if your liver can handle
it. Anavar is a good drug, but it's only
good sublingually. Not. And what are
they going to charge you? They're going
to charge you like $700 a month for some
dissolving wafer of anavar to go under
your tongue when you could just make get
the raw Anavar, mix some DMSO and
propyline glycol, shake it up in a
bottle, and stick it under your tongue.
Like it's so much easier to do stuff
yourself than to trust someone who's
incompetent. And you're like, "Well, I
don't have a chemistry degree. Neither
does the [__] lab tech." The people
at the compoundies don't have degrees.
What the [__] are you thinking? There's
some pharmacists laughing all the way to
the bank and then there's a bunch of
peeons that make $8 an hour that are
working under him that don't give a [__]
about you. At least you care about you.
Nobody can do a better job taking care
of you than you. That's why I went to
medical school. It's like I'm if I don't
take care of myself, I'm going to
[__] die. These [__] don't know a
goddamn thing. And they don't give a
[__] about anyone but themselves and
paying their alimony. So, I better go
and take myself to medical school so I
can survive. So, to answer the question,
Nanderlone is pretty much a [__] drug. I
have seen good results with nandrallone
only, but my IGF-1 was [__] the whole
time. So in the end, yes, testosterone
is problematic because it can have gyno
from the estrogen. It can cause hair
loss from the DHT. That's why I'm a big
believer that you use HRT levels of test
and you use GH and a safe anabolic as a
primary growth agent. So some people
like Primo. The problem is Primo is
going to crush your estrogen, which
means you have to raise your test to
keep your estrogen high, which means
your DHT goes up. So the primo puts you
in a position to where DHT makes your
hair fall out because they want to avoid
mastron because they think mastron
causes hair to fall out. But mastron
doesn't make hair fall out like test
does. And that when you use primo you
have to use a [__] ton of test. So a
thousand test 800 primo you're going to
lose more hair than 200 test and 1,600
mastron. And people are like that's
insane doses. I'm like, that's prolevel
doses because that's what everyone
thinks they should do. That I want to
look like a pro, but I don't want to do
the diet and training. So, I'm just
going to take the steroids that the pros
take. All right.
If you don't have the muscle
that then the steroids don't go to the
muscle, they go to the other areas like
your skin, your hair, your prostate.
that that that the reason why little
guys who use a lot of steroids get more
side effects than big guys who use a lot
of steroids is because the steroids go
where the muscle is. If you don't have
any muscle, so if you have 30 pounds of
muscle, like a normal adult man, then
you can't there's no reason to use the
same amount of steroids that a guy with
150 pounds of muscle uses. So if he's
using three grams, you shouldn't be
using more than 400 milligrams because
you're a little person. You might have a
lot of fat, but you're a little man. And
that a lot of people they I want to be a
big man. It's like that should have
started when you were eight years old.
You should have thought I want to be a
big man when I'm eight. And you should
have been doing push-ups and pull-ups
and eating your meat and eating your
vegetables the whole [__] time. The
whole [__] time. You can't be 40 or
50 years old, be 300 pounds, and have
heart disease and cholesterol and you're
like, I'm just going to start shooting a
pro levels of drugs and turn into
Superman overnight. You got to take it
all the way down to the very bottom. Get
all the fat off your body. Clean out all
your organs. Be super healthy. Even if
you look like a runner, and then start
building up with HRT until you bring
yourself up to the maximum human level,
like Steve Rogers from the first Captain
America movie. Once you look like that,
that's when you would be like, "Okay,
I'm going to add in Masteron or I'm
going to add in a tiny drop of DHB." And
then you will explode for the next year.
You don't have to increase your dose. 20
milligrams of mastron or 10 milligrams
of DHB per day. If you keep training
right and keep eating right, going from
Steve Rogers, you will eventually start
to look like Thor. And then once you
look like Thor and then you're like, I'm
not growing anymore. Okay, you can go to
40 milligrams of Master or 30 Master and
10 DHB. And then you start to look like
the Hulk and be like, there's no way
that that little amount of gear is going
to have that big of an impact. First of
all, you're not multiplying by seven.
And then second of all, I'm saying after
20 years of lifting and eating right,
using small doses of steroids, you will
be healthy and you will also be jacked
and you will be lean and jacked.
That the idea that people are, you know,
there's some influencers that say, "Oh,
gain 30 pounds of muscle in two weeks
using this cycle so that you click on
this video and you watch it." That's
that clickbait [__] I [__] hate
clickbait [__] It's all the [__]
time on the same [__] channels the
primagogs are pushing their clickbait
[__] which is they want to get your
views. They don't give a [__] if the
information they say is true. They don't
care what happens to you. They just want
views because they monetize the channel
and they make money the more views they
get. My channel's not monetized because
I don't give a [__] if I get views
because I'm gonna tell the truth. And if
I tell the truth, I'll get banned if I'm
monetized.